var questions = [{
  "question": "Who won the nomination of the Democratic Party to run for president in 2016?",
  "option1": "Al Gore",
  "option2": "Bernie Sanders",
  "option3": "Hillary Clinton",
  "option4": "Bill Clinton",
  "answer": "3"
}, {
  "question": "Who was the vice president that served under President Barack Obama?",
  "option1": "Evam Bayh",
  "option2": "Joe Biden",
  "option3": "Tim Kaine",
  "option4": "Kathleen Sebelius",
  "answer": "2"
}, {
  "question": "What late American singer was the mayor of Palm Springs California from 1988 to 1992?",
  "option1": "Jerry Butler",
  "option2": "Martha Reeves",
  "option3": "Jon Fishman",
  "option4": "Sonny Bono",
  "answer": "4"
}, {
  "question": "Who was vice president of the United States when Lincoln was assassinated?",
  "option1": "Andrew Johnson",
  "option2": "Hannibal Hamlin",
  "option3": "James S. Sherman",
  "option4": "Millard Fillmore",
  "answer": "1",
}, {
  "question": "Who is the oldest person to be elected to the office of President of the United States?",
  "option1": "Ronald Reagan",
  "option2": "William H. Harrison",
  "option3": "Donald Trump",
  "option4": "James Buchanan",
  "answer": "3"
}, {
  "question": "The oldest parliament in the world belongs to what country?",
  "option1": "Iceland",
  "option2": "United Kingdom",
  "option3": "Denmark",
  "option4": "Japan",
  "answer": "1"
}, {
  "question": "Barack Obama was first elected president of the United States in what year?",
  "option1": "2012",
  "option2": "2008",
  "option3": "2009",
  "option4": "2007",
  "answer": "2"
}, {
  "question": "How many U.S. presidents were only children?",
  "option1": "3",
  "option2": "14",
  "option3": "20",
  "option4": "None",
  "answer": "4"
}, {
  "question": "Who was the first Roman Catholic to be Vice President of the United States of America?",
  "option1": "Al Gore",
  "option2": "Dan Quayle",
  "option3": "Joe Biden",
  "option4": "Dick Cheney",
  "answer": "3"
}, {
  "question": "Who was the first First Lady to be elected to public office?",
  "option1": "Bird Johnson",
  "option2": "Edith Wilson",
  "option3": "Hillary Rodham Clinton",
  "option4": "Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis",
  "answer": "3"
}, {
  "question": "How many US Supreme Court justices are there?",
  "option1": "3",
  "option2": "9",
  "option3": "8",
  "option4": "12",
  "answer": "2"
}];
